[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are several types of broccoli that are very common around the world. Which of these is one of them?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Romanesco broccoli", "Sprouting broccoli", "Purple cauliflower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these condiments has a high salt content and can pretty much fulfill the need for table salt?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish sauce", "Soy sauce", "Oyster sauce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a separate species of scorpions which have two tails, with a venomous sting on each tail.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A wedge of what fruit is traditionally used as a garnish of the Cuba Libre cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Lime", "incorrect_answers": ["Pineapple", "Lemon", "Apple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country was home to the Moa?", "correct_answer": "New Zealand", "incorrect_answers": ["Puerto Rico", "Indonesia", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the Fujita scale in the late 1960s?", "correct_answer": "Theodore Fujita", "incorrect_answers": ["Patrick Fujita", "Calvin Fujita", "Alvin Fujita"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Meet the Robinsons, what was the reasoning that the gym teacher had given for his being allowed to judge the science fair?", "correct_answer": "It was his gym.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was forced to by the administration.", "He fell in love with a student and needed to be near her.", "He had always loved science."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is smallest (by territory)?", "correct_answer": "San Marino", "incorrect_answers": ["Seychelles", "Liechtenstein", "Marshall Islands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the lemur Aye-aye classified according to its diet?", "correct_answer": "Omnivore", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbivore", "Carnivore", "Specialized eater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of John Candys character in the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Del Griffith", "incorrect_answers": ["Del Griffin", "Del Griffing", "Dale Griffith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On this day in 1929, a massacre of mob members outside a warehouse on Clark Street in Chicago occurred. As people walk the street at night they claim to hear the sounds of machine guns and screams.", "correct_answer": "Valentines Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Christmas Day", "Thanksgiving Day", "Easter Sunday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most alluring combination that a woman should represent, according to the sexist correspondent in the 2009 romantic comedy The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "Librarian and stripper", "incorrect_answers": ["Teacher and prostitute", "Angelina Jolie and Pamela Anderson", "Housewife and lover"]}]